# **Ja-Yuan Pendley**

Brooklyn, NY 11235 (347) 496-2445 jay.pendley1218@gmail.com

### **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

Highly skilled and reliable Business Analyst with a superb customer satisfaction record. Adept at interdepartmental coordination to maximize business functionality and efficiency. Committed to ongoing professional development and research to ensure currency and innovation in management and problem-solving. Competent, experienced, organized, enthusiastic, with the ability to provide a focused approach to managing Data, and analytical and exceptional evaluation skills, along with statistics processing, analytical and presentation, and development can be applied. Extremely knowledgeable in Data Analysis. Identify the needs of a business and connect them with information technology (IT) resources to increase sales, strengthen processes and improve efficiency. Act as a mediator and facilitator for all business systems.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Cyquent

**Business Analyst Consultant** 

September 2022- June 2023

- Facilitated weekly Agile "lunch and learns" for the BA and QA audience.
- Involved in reviewing and approving high level and low-level design documents.
- Created data point gap analysis documents, meeting with system users, business, and key people from cross functional applications.
- Translate and simplify requirements for optimizing execution and outcomes.
- Develop business and technical requirements and review Requirements.
- Work with waterfall
- Collaborate directly with business stakeholders, clients, designers, developers, and engineers to ensure the applications are built
  according to specifications and delivered on schedule.
- Data Conversion

## **New York Institute of Technology**

September 2021 – October 2022

## **Technical Data Analyst- Part-Time Position**

- Responsible to collect, clean, transforming, and validating data as a process to Obtain conclusions.
- Present data in the form of charts, graphs, and tables for immediate reference.
- Presents an analysis of all data to senior management.
- Collaborated with stakeholder groups across the organization to ensure business and technology alignment.
- Coordinates with all key or authorized staff with the distribution of data analysis
- Coordinate with technical analysts, and before publishing client reports
- Monitors and organizes all client invoices for the purpose of accurate and timely billing procedures
- Maintains and updates all data archives
- Utilize data and technology to create positive change and help the business thrive.

## Franklin D. Roosevelt High School

February 2018- June 2020

#### IT Support / Data Analyst Brooklyn, NY

- Configured hardware, devices, and software to set up workstations for employees.
- Provided onsite technical support for 300 employees ensuring hardware and software applications are resolved.
- Responsible to enter data of all computers and printers for all staff.
- Collaborated with supervisors to escalate and address customer inquiries or technical issues.

# **Ja-Yuan Pendley**

#### PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- Tableau (Beginner) <u>Tableau Portfolio</u>
- Plotly (intermediate)
- Seaborn
- Matplotlib
- Data Analysis
- Statistical Analysis
- Neutral Network
- Python (Keras, Scikit-learn)
- Python, Databases (MySQL)

- Data manipulation
- SQL (CTE, Remove Null Value, Create tables, & Dashboards.)
- Machine Learning
- Use of MS Suite and various other software.
- Create and implement precise management plans with attention to transparent communication.
- Collaborated with key personnel in analyzing business requests for feasibility and costs.

#### **EDUCATION**

- New York Institute of Technology Master of Science, Data Science
- New York City College of Technology Bachelor of Computer Systems Technology
- Published Works: My Portfolio